Guide to the Hanover Royal Music Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Duke of Cumberland's Band Archive, circa 1765-1834; Series III; 9; (107 boxes)
  - Logier, Johann Bernhard, d. 1846
    - A Sett of Quick and Slow Marches, Troops &c… Parts (2 fl (1 part), 2 cl, 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn (1 part), 2 tpt (1 part)). Print (Dublin: for the author), undated (Box 236, Folder 1236-1237)
      Original folder: numbered 2
    - Slow March. Kilkenny. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, 3 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 236, Folder 1238-1239)
      Original folder: numbered 1
  - Logier, Johann Bernhard, d. 1846, arranger
    - The Celebrated Music of Macbeth…. Parts (2 fl, 3 cl, 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn, tpt). Print (Dublin: Holden), undated (Box 236, Folder 1240-1241)
  - Mainvielle-Fodor, Mme. (Joséphone), 1789-1870
    See: Unidentified
  - Mansfield, arranger
    - Military music. Miss McLea's Farewell. Parts (4 fl (3 parts), 2 cl, 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 236, Folder 1242-1243)
      Original folder: numbered 61
  - Martín y Soler, Vicente, 1754-1806
    - [L'arbore di Diana. Excerpts]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt (1 part)). Manuscript, undated (Box 237, Folder 1244-1245)
      Original folder: numbered 27, 44, and 292
    - [L'arbore di Diana. Excerpts]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (fl, 2 cl, ob, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 237, Folder 1246-1247)
      Original folder: numbered 27 and 292a
    - [Una cosa rara]. Opera Lilla. Parts (4 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 237-238, Folder 1248-1252)
      Original folder: numbered 1 and 223
  - Martini, Johann Paul Aegidius, 1741-1816
    - [Henri IV. Overture]. Parts (2 fl, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 239, Folder 1253-1254)
      Original folder: numbered 37
    - [Henri IV. Overture]. Parts (2 vn, 2 va (1 part), b, 2 ob, 2 bn (1 part), 2 hn, 2 tpt). Print (no publisher information), undated (Box 239, Folder 1255-1256)
      Original folder: numbered 44 and 50
  - Mayr, Giovanni Simone, 1763-1845
    - [Adelaide di Guesclino. Overture]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 239-240, Folder 1257-1258)
      Original folder: numbered 26, 43, and 85
    - [Adelaide di Guesclino. Overture]. Mayers Celebrated Overture to the Opera of Adelaide…. Arranged by John Collier. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 5 cl (4 parts), 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn (1 part)). Print (London: W. Milhouse), undated (Box 240, Folder 1259)
      Original folder: not present; music numbered 14 and 82
  - Méhul, Etienne Nicolas, 1763-1817
    See also: Kreutzer, Rodolphe, 1766-1831
    - [L'irato. Excerpts]. Ouverture et Airs D'Irato…. Arranged by M. Ozi. Parts (2 cl 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (Paris: Pleyel), undated (Box 240, Folder 1260-1262)
      Original folder: numbered 66 and 80
  - Mezger
    - [Concerto, flute, orchestra]. Parts (fl, 2 vn, vla, b, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 240, Folder 1263-1264)
      Original folder: numbered 36 and 2
  - Monzani, Tebaldo, 1762-1839
    - [Polacca]. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, 1805? (Box 241, Folder 1265-1266)
      Original folder: numbered 10 and 285
      Watermark: 1805
      With: additional parts in an unidentified 20th century hand
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791
    See also: Winter, Peter von
    See also: Unidentified
    - [La clemenza di Tito. Overture]. A Set of Harmonia. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 cl, 3 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 241, Folder 1267-1270)
      Original folder: numbered 25, 42, and 207
      Includes arrangments of other works by Mozart
    - [La clemenza di Tito. Excerpts]. Six of the most Favorite Pieces From the Grand Serious sopera La Clemenza di Tito. Arranged. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn). Print (London: M. Kelly), undated (Box 242, Folder 1271-1273)
      Original folder: numbered 56
    - [La clemenza di Tito. Excerpts]. Marches In the Opera…. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 242, Folder 1274-1275)
      Original folder: numbered 23 and 215
    - [La clemenza di Tito. Excerpts]. Arranged. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 242-243, Folder 1276-1280)
      Original folder: numbered 6
    - [Così fan tutte. Excerpts]. Douze Nouvelles Suites d'harmonie…Suivies de Marches et pas Redoublés par J. Gebauer… 1 Livraison. Arranged by Michael Joseph Gebauer. Parts (2 fl, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (Paris: Sieber), undated (Box 244, Folder 1281-1282)
      Original folder: numbered 8 and 114
    - [Don Giovanni. Ah, taci ingiusto core!]. Andante. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 c. 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt (1 part), trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 244, Folder 1283-1284)
      Original folder: numbered 1 and 130
    - [Don Giovanni. Or sai chi l'onore]. Andante. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (2 fl, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 244, Folder 1285-1286)
      Original folder: numbered 13 and 132
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (4 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 245, Folder 1287-1288)
      Original folder: numbered 14 and 208
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Oboe Parts from The German Operas. Arranged. Parts (2 ob, 2nd cl, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 245, Folder 1289-1292)
      With: Dittersdorf, Karl Ditters von. [Liebe im Narrenhaus. Excerpts]. Arranged by Keil. Parts (2nd ob). Manuscript
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 246, Folder 1293-1295)
      Original folder: numbered 4 and 210
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Arranged. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 246-247, Folder 1296-1299)
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Arranged. Parts (1st cl, 2 bn). Manuscript, undated (Box 247, Folder 1300)
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 247, Folder 1301-1303)
      Original folder: numbered 3
    - [Don Giovanni. Excerpts]. Parts (2 cl (1 part), spt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 248, Folder 1304)
      Watermark: 1803
    - [Die Entführung aus dem Serail. Excerpts]. Arranged. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 248, Folder 1305-1307)
      Original folder: numbered 7 and 216
    - [Le nozze di Figaro. Overture]. Arranged by John Collier. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 6 cl, 3 bn, spt, 3 hn, 3 tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 248-249, Folder 1308-1310)
      Watermarks: 1807-1812
    - [Quartet, strings, K. 387, G major; K. 421, D minor]. [Quartet, strings, K. 458, B flat major]. Three Quartetts…. Parts (2 vn, va, vc). Print (London: L. Lavenu), circa 1797 (Box 249, Folder 1311-1312)
      Original folder: numbered 10 and 21
    - [Quintet, violins, violas, violoncello, K. 614, E-flat major]. Harmonie Pour Deux Clarinettes, Deux Bassons, et Deux Cors. Arranged. Parts (2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (London: Broderip & Wilkinson), undated (Box 249, Folder 1313-1314)
      Original folder: numbered 20 and 41
    - [Der Schauspieldirector. Overture]. Arranged by John Collier. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 5 cl, 3 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 250, Folder 1315-1316)
      Original folder: numbered 37, 137, and 83
    - [Symphony]. No. 1 of Mozart's Grand Symphonies, Arranged as Sestettos…. Arranged by J. B. Cimador. Parts (2 vn, 2 vla, vc, b, fl, 2 ob, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, timp). Print (London: for Monzani), undated (Box 250, Folder 1317-1319)
      Original folder: numbered 8 and 62
      Serpent and trombone parts in manuscript
    - [Zauberflöte. Overture]. Mozart's Favorite Overture of Zauberflote…. Parts (2 vn, vla, vc and b (1 part), vc and b (1 part, ms), 2 fl (1 part), 2 cl (1 part), 2 ob (1 part), 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn (1 part), 2 tpt (1 part), 2 trbn (1 part), timp). Print (London), undated (Box 251, Folder 1320-1321)
      Original folder: numbered 40
    - [Zauberflöte. Excerpts]. Arranged by Schäfer. Parts (4 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt (1 part)). Manuscript, 1802? (Box 251-252, Folder 1322-1326)
      Original folder: numbered 9
      Watermarks: 1801-1804
    - [Unidentified]. Douze Nouvelles Suites d'harmonie…Suivies de Marches et pas Redoublés par J. Gebauer… 9 Livraison. Arranged by Michael Joseph Gebauer. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 hn (1 part)). Parts for Gebauer (miniature, uncut: fl, 3 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn tpt, tpt, trbn, bass drum and cymbal (1 part)). Print (Paris: Sieber), undated (Box 252, Folder 1327-1328)
    - [Unidentified]. Two Favorite Pieces. Arranged by Frederick Eley. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 252, Folder 1329-1330)
      Original folder: numbered 18 and 146
  - Müller
    - [Duets, flute, violin]. Six Duos pour Flûte et Violon…. Op. 9. Parts (fl, vn). Print (Offenbach: Jean André), undated (Box 253, Folder 1331-1332)
  - Neubauer
    - [Symphony]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 253, Folder 1333-1335)
      Original folder: numbered 16 and 103
    - [Symphony]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 253, Folder 1336-1337)
      Original folder: numbered 20 and 100
  - Norris, Thomas, 1741-1790
    - [Symphonies]. Six Simphonies…. Op. 1. Parts (2 vn, vla, vc, 2 ob, 2 bn (1 part), 2 hn). Print (London: for the author and sold by Mr. Welcker), circa 1765 (Box 254, Folder 1338-1341)
  - Orson
    - [Valentine. Excerpts]. 5 Favorite Pieces in Valentine. Arranged by Frederick Eley. Parts (4 fl, 2 cl, 2 bn (1 part), 2 hn (1 part), tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 254, Folder 1342-1343)
      Original folder: numbered 10 and 234
  - Paër, Ferdinando, 1771-1839
    See: Blayney, J., arranger
  - Paisiello, Giovanni, 1740-1816
    - [Frascatana. Excerpts]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 255, Folder 1344-1345)
      Original folder: numbered 38 and 238
  - Pick, Henry
    - Andantino. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 255, Folder 1346-1347)
      Original folder: numbered 20 and 37
    - A Set of Military Divertisments…. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 4 cl (2 parts), 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt, timp). Print (London: for the editor by Broderip & Wilkinson), undated (Box 255-256, Folder 1348-1350)
      Original folder: numbered 2 and 178
    - A Second Set of Military Divertisments…. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 4 cl (3 parts), 2 bn and spt (2 parts), 2 hn (1 part), tpt). Print (London: for the editor by Broderip & Wilkinson), undated (Box 256, Folder 1351-1353)
      Original folder: numbered 3 and 177
    - A Third Set of Military Divertisments…. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 4 cl (3 parts), 2 bn and spt (2 parts), 2 hn (1 part), tpt). Print (London: for the editor by Broderip & Wilkinson), undated (Box 257, Folder 1354-1356)
      Original folder: numbered 4 and 196
    - 4th Set of Military Music. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 2 cl, 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn, tpt). Print (no publisher information), undated (Box 257-258, Folder 1357-1359)
  - Pick, Henry, arranger
    - Grand Waltz. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 258, Folder 1360-1361)
      Original folder: numbered 34 and 284
    - Iphigenia in Aulida. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 258, Folder 1362-1363)
      Original folder: numbered 24 and 237
      With: arrangements of other pieces by Mozart and Gluck
    - The King's March. Parts (fl, 2 cl, 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt and drum/cymbals (1 part)). Manuscript, undated (Box 258, Folder 1364-1365)
    - No. 1 of Periodical Grand Military Pieces Arranged from the Works of Celebrated Composers…. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 2 cl, 2 bn and spt (2 parts), 2 hn (1 part), tpt, timp). Print (London: Broderip & Wilkinson), undated (Box 258, Folder 1366-1367)
    - Occasional Overture. Parts (ob, 3 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 259, Folder 1368-1369)
      Original folder: numbered 2 and 92
    - [Peeping Tom of Coventry. Overture]. Parts (2 fl, 2 cl, 2 bn and spt (2 parts), hn). Manuscript, 1797? (Box 259, Folder 1370-1372)
      Original folder: numbered 19, 36, and 86
      Watermark: 1797
      With: Princess Augusta's Favourite; and other pieces.
    - Military Music. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt, trbn). Manuscript, 1798? (Box 259, Folder 1373-1374)
      Original folder: numbered 22 and 191
      Watermark: 1798
    - Military Music. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 4 cl (3 parts), 2 bn, spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 260, Folder 1375-1377)
      Original folder: numbered 12 and 197
    - Serenate. Parts (2 fl, 6 cl, 4 bn, spt, 4 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 260-261, Folder 1378-1381)
      Original folder: numbered 21 and 122
    - A Set of Military Music. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 261, Folder 1382-1383)
      Original folder: numbered 25 and 192
    - A Sett of Military Music. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, bass drum). Manuscript, undated (Box 261, Folder 1384-1385)
      Original folder: numbered 28 and 190
    - A Sett of Military Music. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 3 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, great drum). Manuscript, undated (Box 262, Folder 1386-1387)
      Original folder: numbered 30 and 198
    - A Set of Military Music. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt (1 part), trbn, 2 drum). Manuscript, undated (Box 262, Folder 1388-1390)
      Original folder: numbered 33 and 200
    - A Sett of Military Music. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 262, Folder 1391-1392)
      Original folder: numbered 29 and 195
    - A Sett of Psalms. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 263, Folder 1393-1394)
      Original folder: numbered 26 and 156
    - Rondo. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn (1 part), tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 263, Folder 1395-1396)
      Original folder: numbered 35 and 123
  - Pleyel, Ignaz, 1757-1831
    - Andantino con Variationi. Parts (2 fl, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn). Manuscript, 1802? (Box 263, Folder 1397-1398)
      Original folder: numbered 47 and 133
    - [Concerto, violoncello, orchestra]. A Concerto for the Violoncello…. Parts (solo vc, 2 vn, 2 va, b, 2 ob, 2 hn). Print (London: Forster), undated (Box 263, Folder 1399-1400)
      Original folder: numbered 31
    - [Duets, flute, violin]. Trois Duos pour Flûte et Violons, ou deux Violons…Livre 3me. Parts (fl, vn). Print (Offenbach: J. André), undated (Box 264, Folder 1401-1402)
    - [Duets, violins]. Sei Duetti per due violini…. Op. 5. Parts (2 vn). Print ([Vienna: Artaria]), 1788 (Box 264, Folder 1403-1404)
      Original folder: numbered 16
      Inscribed: Printz Ernst August Göttingen…22ten. Dec. 1790
    - [Partita]. Parthia. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 hn, 2 bn). Manuscript, undated (Box 264, Folder 1405-1406)
      Original folder: numbered 30 and 138
    - [Quartet. Excerpt]. Divertimento. Arranged by Henry Liebe. Parts (2 fl, 3 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 264, Folder 1407-1408)
      Original folder: numbered 15 and 171
    - [Quartets]. Six Quatuors tirés de l'Oeuvre 34me…Livre 1. Arranged by Devienne. Parts (fl, vn, va, vc). Print (Offenbach: J. André), undated (Box 265, Folder 1409-1410)
    - [Quartets]. Six Quatuors tirés de l'Oeuvre 34me… Livre 2. Arranged by Devienne. Parts (fl, vn, va, vc). Print (Offenbach: J. André), undated (Box 265, Folder 1411-1412)
      Original folder: numbered 9 and 28
    - [Quartets, strings]. Three Quartettos…. Op.9. A Fourth Sett. Parts (2 vn, vc). Print (London: for W. Forster), undated (Box 265, Folder 1413-1414)
      Original folder: numbered 14 and 24
    - [Quartets, strings]. Three Quartettos…Op.9…Book 3. Parts (2 vn, va, vc). Print (London: for Forster), undated (Box 266, Folder 1415-1416)
      Original folder: numbered 13 and 23
    - [Quintets, violins, violas, violoncello]. Trois Quintettos…Op.8. Parts (2 vn, 2 va, vc). Print (London: Longman & Broderip), undated (Box 266, Folder 1417-1418)
      Original folder: numbered 45
    - [Sinfonie concertante, flute, oboe, bassoon, 2 violins, viola, violoncello]. Pleyel's celebrated Concertante in F…. Parts (4 vn, 2 va, vc, 2 b, 2 fl (1 ms), 2 ob (1 ms), 2 bn (1 ms), 2 hn, trbn). Print (London: Clementi, Banger, Hyde, Collard & Davis), undated (Box 266-267, Folder 1419-1422)
  - Purcell, Henry, 1659-1695
    - War Song. Come if You Dare. Arranged by Frederick Eley. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, 1802? (Box 267, Folder 1423-1424)
      Original folder: numbered 12 and 254
  - Reeve, William, 1757-1815
  - Reicha, Anton, 1770-1836
    - [Symphony]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 f, 2 ob, 5 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 267, Folder 1425-1427)
      Original folder: numbered 17 and 99
  - Reid, John, 1721-1807
    - [Marches]. Twelve Marches…. Arranged by Winter. Parts (fl, 4 cl, 2 hn (1 part), 2 bn (1 part), spt). Print (London: Preston), undated (Box 268, Folder 1428-1429)
      Original folder: numbered 67
  - Righini, Vincenzo, 1756-1812
    - [Partita, woodwinds, horns (2), E-flat major]. Serenate pour deux Clarinettes deux Cors & deux Bassons…. Parts (cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (Leipzig: Schmiedt & Rau), undated (Box 268, Folder 1430-1431)
  - Rosetti, Antonio, ca. 1750-1792
    - [Harmonie, 2 oboes, 2 clarinets, 2 bassoons, 2 horns]. Harmonie…. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (Paris: Pleyel), undated (Box 268, Folder 1432-1433)
      Original folder: numbered 43 and 161
  - Rosselli, Agrippino, fl. 1784-1800
    - Grand Military Parthia. Arranged by Frederick Eley. Parts (2 fl, 6 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 268, Folder 1434-1435)
      Original folder: numbered 15 and 139
  - Rousseau, Jean-Jacques, 1712-1778
  - Schaffner, Nicolaus Albert, b. ca. 1790
    - La Chasse: Ouverture en Harmonie…. Arranged by Vincent Gambaro. Parts (1 fl. 4 cl, 2 bn (1 part), spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt (1 part), trbn). Print (Paris: Gambaro), undated (Box 269, Folder 1436-1437)
      Original folder: numbered 69 and 93
  - Schetky, G. (George), 1776-1831
    - A Collection of Scottish Music…. Parts (2 fl (1 part), 2 cl, bn, 2 hn, tpt). Print (London: Broderip & Wilkinson), undated (Box 269, Folder 1438-1439)
      Original folder: numbered 38 and 53
  - Schmittbaur, Joseph Aloys
    - [Quartets, flute, violin, viola, violoncello, op. 3]. III Quatuors…. Parts (fl, vn, va, b). Print (Vienna: Artaria), circa 1775 (Box 269, Folder 1440-1441)
      Original folder: numbered 15
      One quartet for flute, 2 violins, and violoncello
  - Severitz, George
    - A Grand Military Concertante…. Parts (2 fl, 3 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Print (London: W. Milhouse), undated (Box 270, Folder 1442-1443)
      Original folder: numbered 48 and 159
    - A Grand Piece for a Military Band…. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Print (London: W. Milhouse), undated (Box 270, Folder 1444-1445)
  - Steibelt, Daniel, 1765-1823
    - [La belle laitière. Excerpt]. Arranged. The Shawl Dance By Madame Parisot…. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, 1802? (Box 270, Folder 1446-1447)
      Original folder: numbered 9 and 245
    - [La belle laitière. Excerpt]. Arranged by Frederick Eley. Pas de Trois…. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn). Manuscript, undated (Box 271, Folder 1448-1449)
      Original folder: numbered 13 and 244
    - [La belle laitière. Excerpt]. Arranged by Frederick Eley. Allegretto…. Parts (2 fl, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt). Manuscript, undated (Box 271, Folder 1450-1451)
      Original folder: numbered 3 and 246
  - Sterkel, Johann Franz Xaver, 1750-1817
    - [Symphony]. A Grand Symphony…. Arranged by John Collier. Parts (2 fl, 6 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Print (London: W. Milhouse), undated (Box 271, Folder 1452-1454)
    - [Symphony]. Sinfonie à grand Orchestre…No.6…. Parts (2 vn, va, b, 2 fl, 2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn (1 part), 2 hn, 2 tpt). Print (Leipzig: Breitkopf & Härtel), circa 1810 (Box 272, Folder 1455-1457)
      Original folder: numbered 3 and 66
  - Stumpf, Johann Christian
    - Three Grand Pieces…. Arranged by W. Bies. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, timp). Print (London: W. Milhouse), undated (Box 272, Folder 1458-1459)
      Original folder: numbered 70
    - Harmonia in C. Arranged by John Collier. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 6 cl, 3 bn, 2 spt, 4 hn, 2 tpt, 3 trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 272-273, Folder 1460-1465)
      Original folder: numbered 39 and 29
      On parts: Three Favorite Pieces Selected from the Work of Stumff…
    - Harmonia in C, con Variationi. Arranged by John Collier. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 7 cl, 3 bn, spt, 3 hn, 3 tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 274, Folder 1466-1468)
      Original folder: numbered 36 and 127
    - [Harmonies]. Suites d'Harmonie, undated (Box 274, Folder 1469)
      Original folder only
      Original folder: numbered 57
    - [Harmonies]. Douze Nouvelles Suites d'harmonie…Suivies de Marches et pas Redoublés par J. Gebauer…Suite 112…5me. Livraison…. Parts (2 vn, 2 va, vc and b (1 part), 2 fl, 2 ob, 2 bn, 2 hn, 2 tpt, timp). Print (Paris: Sieber père), undated (Box 274, Folder 1470-1471)
    - [Harmonies]. Douze Nouvelles Suites d'harmonie…Suivies de Marches et pas Redoublés par J. Gebauer…Suite 115…8e. Livraison…. Parts (2 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (Paris: Sieber père), undated (Box 275, Folder 1472-1473)
    - [Harmonies]. Douze Nouvelles Suites d'harmonie…Suivies de Marches et pas Redoublés par J. Gebauer…Suite 117…10me. Livraison…. Parts (4 ob, 2 cl, 2 bn, 2 hn). Print (Paris: Sieber père), undated (Box 275, Folder 1474-1475)
      Original folder: numbered 14 and 124
      Two oboe parts in manuscript
  - Tuch, H. A. G.
    - Grosser Trauer Marsch…. Op. 40. Parts (fl, 2 cl, 2 bn, spt, 4 hn, tpt, trbn). Print (Dessau and Leipzig: im Musik Comptoir), undated (Box 275, Folder 1476-1477)
      Original folder: numbered 71
  - Venua, F.
    - [Don Quichotte. Act I]. Ballet of Don Quichotte ou Les Noces de Gamache. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob. 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, tpt, trbn). Manuscript, 1809 June 5 (Box 276, Folder 1478-1482)
      Original folder: numbered 10 and 242
    - [Don Quichotte. Act II]. Ballet of Don Quichotte ou Les Noces de Gamache. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn). Manuscript, undated (Box 277-278, Folder 1483-1488)
      Original folder: numbered 11 and 241
  - Viotti, Giovanni Battista, 1755-1824
    - [Quartets, flute, violin, viola, violoncello]. Three Quartetts Serenatas…Book 1. Op.25. Parts (fl, vn, va, vc). Print (London: Clementi, Banger, Hyde, Collard & Davis), undated (Box 279, Folder 1489-1490)
      Original folder: numbered 24
  - Vogel, Johann Christoph, 1756-1788
    - [Quartets, clarinet, violin, viola, violoncello]. Three Favourite Quartetts…. Parts (cl, vn, va, vc). Print (London: W. Milhouse), undated (Box 279, Folder 1491-1492)
      Original folder: numbered 8
  - Weber, Carl Maria von, 1786-1826
  - Weigl, Joseph, 1766-1846
    - [L'uniforme. Overture]. Arranged by Henry Pick. Parts (2 fl, 2 ob, 4 cl, 2 bn, spt, 2 hn, 2 tpt, trbn, timp). Manuscript, undated (Box 279, Folder 1493-1494)
      Original folder: numbered 24, 41 and 78